<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UT Lot Locator</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="permit_selector">Select Permit</string>
    <string name="title_activity_permitselector">permit selector</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to the UT Lot Locator! Please select your permit type and press GO!</string>
    <string name="go">GO!</string>
    <string name="l70_title">Lot 70</string>
    <string name="l37m_title">Lot 37 - Motorcycle</string>
    <string name="l37c_title">Lot 37 - C Spots</string>
    <string name="m21st_title">Motorcycle Spots - 21st</string>
    <string name="l35_title">Longhorn Lot 35</string>
    <string name="l113_title">Longhorn Lot 113</string>
    <string name="l103_title">Longhorn Lot 103</string>
    <string name="l118_title">Longhorn Lot 118</string>
    <string name="l108_title">Longhorn Lot 108</string>
    <string name="l104_title">Longhorn Lot 104</string>
    <string name="l117_title">Longhorn Lot 117</string>
    <string name="l119_title">Longhorn Lot 119</string>
    <string name="l115_title">Longhorn Lot 115</string>
    <string name="l109_title">Longhorn Lot 109</string>
    <string name="l114_title">Longhorn Lot 114</string>
    <string name="l110_title">Longhorn Lot 110</string>
    <string name="l112_title">Longhorn Lot 112</string>
    <string name="l116_title">Longhorn Lot 116</string>
    <string name="l107_title">Longhorn Lot 107</string>
    <string name="ccg_title">Conference Center Garage (CCG)</string>
    <string name="brg_title">Brazos Garage (BRG)</string>
    <string name="gug_title">Guadalupe Garage (GUG)</string>
    <string name="mag_title">Manor Garage (MAG)</string>
    <string name="sag_title">San Antonio Garage (SAG)</string>
    <string name="sjg_title">San Jacinto Garage (SJG)</string>
    <string name="swg_title">Speedway Garage (SWG)</string>
    <string name="trg_title">Trinity Garage (TRG)</string>
    <string name="tsg_title">27th Street Garage (TSG)</string>
    <string name="mDk_title">Motorcycle Spots - Dean Keaton and Robert Dedman</string>
    <string name="mRdm_title">Motorcycle Spots - Robert Dedman</string>
    <string name="mTr_title">Motorcycle Spots - Trinity</string>
    <string name="mSw_title">Motorcycle Spots - Speedway and Dean Keaton</string>
    <string name="m27_title">Motorcycle Spots - 27th</string>
    <string name="mWh_title">Motorcycle Spots - Whitis</string>
    <string name="mbur_title">Motorcycle Spots - Behind Burdine</string>
    <string name="m24_title">Motorcycle Spots - 24th</string>
    <string name="mJes_title">Motorcycle Spots - Jester Circle</string>
    <string name="mSjc_title">Motorcycle Spots - San Jacinto</string>
    <string name="mL70S_title">Motorcycle Spots - Lot 70 South Side</string>
    <string name="mL70N_title">Motorcycle Spots - Lot 70 North Side</string>
    <string name="mL118_title">Motorcycle Spots - Lot 118</string>
    <string name="m16_title">Motorcycle Spots - W 16th</string>
    <string name="mL116_title">Motorcycle Spots - Longhorn Lot 116</string>
    <string name="cPermit">C Permit</string>
    <string name="cplusPermit">C+ Permit</string>
    <string name="rPermit">R Permit</string>
    <string name="sPermit">S Permit</string>
    <string name="mPermit">M Permit</string>
    <string name="nPermit">N Permit</string>
    <string name="nplusPermit">N+ Permit</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mapview">MapView</string>
    <string name="cPermitDesc">The C Permit is available to all registered students and those auditing
        classes at the university. This permit allows students to park in any C lots from 6 A.M. to
        4 A.M. daily. Longhorn Lots are also available with this permit 24/7 unless otherwise indicated
        by signs. This permit does not have a limit on sales so parking becomes more challenging
        throughout the day as spaces are taken.</string>
    <string name="cplusPermitDesc">The C+ Permit is available to all registered students and those
        auditing classes at the university. This permit allows students to park in any C lots from
        6 A.M. to 4 A.M. daily. Longhorn Lots are also available with this permit 24/7 unless otherwise
        indicated by signs. This permit also allows students to park in all university garages
        (except CCG) between 5 P.M. and 4 A.M. weekly and all day on weekends (Friday at 5 P.M. to
        Monday at 4 A.M.). This permit does not have a limit on sales so parking becomes more challenging
        throughout the day as spaces are taken.</string>
    <string name="rPermitDesc">The R Permit is available to any UT Austin student who has a UT Housing
        and Food Residence Hall contract. Garage permits offer the most convenient parking options
        for residence halls with many of our garages next to, or across the street from, university
        housing. R permits are valid only in the garage for which they are purchased. Only limited
        numbers of R permits are sold, meaning that in general you should always be able to find a
        parking space. R parking is restricted to the upper level of the garages Monday-Friday, but
        a majority of the spaces available are covered. Nonetheless, you might be required to park
        on the roof at times during the term for your permit. This permit should provide parking for
        you in your assigned garage 24/7, with few exceptions. Occasionally, R permit holders may be
        relocated to accommodate large events. Advanced e-mail notifications will be sent and in
        general, you can expect to be relocated to another garage. Longhorn Lots are also available
        for all permits.</string>
    <string name="sPermitDesc">The S Permit is available to UT students who live off campus (i.e.,
        those who do NOT have an official university residence hall contract). S permits are valid only
        in the garage for which they are purchased. Only limited numbers of S permits are sold, meaning
        that in general you should always be able to find a parking space. S parking is restricted to
        the upper level of the garages Monday-Friday, but a majority of the spaces available are covered.
        Nonetheless, you might be required to park on the roof at times during the term for your permit.
        This permit should provide parking for you in your assigned garage 24/7, with few exceptions.
        This permit is not intended for habitual overnight storage of your vehicle, and this will cost
        an additional storage fee. Occasionally, S permit holders may be relocated to accommodate large
        events. Advanced e-mail notifications will be sent and in general, you can expect to be relocated
        to another garage. Longhorn Lots are also available for all permits.</string>
    <string name="mPermitDesc">The M Permit is available to any affiliate of the university. Intended
        for use with a motorcycle, motor scooter, moped, or motor-assisted bicycles. M permit holders may
        only park in designated motorcycle parking areas from 7:30 a.m. to 3:30 p.m. They may park in
        surface lot automobile spaces after permit restrictions have lifted as indicated by signs; they
        may not park at any time in automobile garage spaces. Vehicle must be parked perpendicular to the
        curb when applicable. Longhorn Lots are available with this permit weekdays after 3:30 p.m. and
        weekends from Friday at 3:30 p.m. to Monday at 7:30 a.m.</string>
    <string name="nPermitDesc">The N Permit is available to students, faculty, staff, and other affiliates.
        N permit holders may park in spaces for \"Any UT Permit\", and Longhorn Lots. Times restricted to
        weeknights between 5:45 p.m. and 7:30 a.m. and all day on weekends from Friday at 5:45 p.m. to
        Monday at 7:30 a.m. (unless otherwise indicated by signs — Note: some Longhorn Lots have no
        parking between 4 a.m. and 6 a.m.).</string>
    <string name="nplusPermitDesc">The N+ Permit is available to students, faculty, staff, and other
        affiliates. Parking is not guaranteed in any particular garage, but is accessible for all garages
        (except the Conference Center Garage - CCG) weeknights between 5 p.m. and 4 a.m. and all day on
        weekends (Friday at 5 p.m. to Monday at 4 a.m.) on a space-available basis. Additionally, the
        N+ Permit grants access to park in Longhorn Lots and spaces signed \"Any UT Permit\" weeknights
        between 5:45 p.m. and 7:30 a.m. and all day on weekends (Friday at 5:45 p.m. to Monday at
        7:30 a.m.).</string>
</resources>
<!--<string-array name="permit_array">-->
<!--<item>C Permit</item>-->
<!--<item>C+ Permit</item>-->
<!--<item>R Permit</item>-->
<!--<item>S Permit</item>-->
<!--<item>M Permit</item>-->
<!--<item>N Permit</item>-->
<!--<item>N+ Permit</item>-->
<!--</string-array>-->
<!--<string name="goole_maps_key" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">-->
        <!--AIzaSyB7Z4b5LbZLFrCGhuUrqPtSqo_pnjORyDU-->
    <!--</string>-->